#### Contact

Lonehill, Sandton +27 72 822 4174 (Mobile) cliff.crerar@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/cliff-crerar (LinkedIn) www.learn-transact-sql.tk (Other) www.quora.com/profile/Cliff-Crerar (Personal)

# Top Skills

Node.js Amazon Web Services (AWS) Microsoft Azure

## Languages

English Afrikaans

### Certifications

ACL Scripting
Structured Query Language

### Honors-Awards

Realtor

#### **Publications**

T-SQL Fundamentals:

# **Clifford Crerar**

< iCode | iBuild | iSolve /> Solutions Architect Johannesburg Area, South Africa

# Summary

In 2014, I started a part-time degree in informatics to be completed in 2019. 2016 I started to self study Javascript along with many of the facets of modern web applications as a hobby. After a fulfilling career as an asset accountant for more than 9 years,I pursued a great career changing opportunity in 2017. Currently involved with in the development of web based applications that run on big name cloud service technologies.

# Experience

SurTech Solutions Solutions Architect June 2018 - Present

Rosebank

ACL Africa ERP Solutions Architect May 2017 - May 2018 (1 year 1 month) Rosebank

i-Chain (Pty) Ltd Asset accounting specialist / Project manager August 2012 - April 2017 (4 years 9 months) Edenburg, Sandton

There is no known competitor in South Africa who can deliver fixed asset management software and related services, project implementation, and a support programme that meets every requirement in terms of GAAP, MFMA, PFMA, GRAP, IFRS and even SARBOX compliance, as we do.

i-Chain achieved milestones in successfully moving several public departments

to an Unqualified Audit Opinion. Where other large consulting firms had previously tried to do the same and failed, only i-Chain had the capability to deliver as a result of our unique approach,

team of experts, focus and leading-edge technology.

When it comes to the creation, correction and management of asset registers our track record, and out-performance of seemingly formidable competitors, speaks for itself.

PwC South Africa Asset Management Consultant March 2008 - July 2012 (4 years 5 months) Menlo Park

Consult and advise on fixed assets. Creation of Fixed Asset Registers with physical and financial information according to client specific accounting policy. Project and people management.

Investments @home Realtor August 2005 - December 2007 (2 years 5 months) Pretoria

Real estate marketing and finding the prospective buyer the right home.

Dros Montana Waitron January 2003 - December 2003 (1 year) Pretoria

# Education

University of South Africa/Universiteit van Suid-Afrika Bachelor of Commerce (B.Com.), Business Informatics · (2015 - 2019)

Udemy Academy
Certification, Learn and Understand NodeJS · (2018 - 2018)

Udemy Academy

Certification, Tomcat server from beginner to advanced

University of South Africa/Universiteit van Suid-Afrika Higher Certificate, Economic and management sciences · (2014 - 2014)

Free Code Camp

Full Stack Development Certification, Computer Software Engineering · (2016 - 2019)